<resources>

    <!-- app -->
    <string name="app_name">Minima</string>
    <string name="title_course">Course</string>
    <string name="title_timetable">Timetable</string>
    <string name="title_setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="action_view">Fionix</string>
    <string name="splash_screen">Splash Screen</string>

    <!-- Intro -->
    <string name="intro1">The developer of this project already complete his studies and he unable to support this application at full-time because he already secured working.</string>
    <string name="intro2">This application already made open-sourced and licensed under GNU General Public License v3.0. Let\'s make Minima better together.</string>
    <string name="intro3">You can contribute by reporting issues, fixed issues reported by using the pull request (PR) and introduce the app to your friends.</string>
    <string name="intro4">Approach the developer if you want to help porting Minima to another platform (such as iOS and Windows Phone) financially. It requires a large amount of cash to develop and publish them.</string>
    <string name="intro5">The application is distributed for free without taking any advantage of the user. Please respect and appreciate his work. Thank you for using Minima.</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>

    <!-- course -->
    <string name="course_add">Add Course</string>
    <string name="course_list">Course List</string>
    <string name="course_faculty">Faculty</string>
    <string name="course_dialog_course_code">Course Code (Ex: EEE610)</string>
    <string name="course_dialog_course_name">Course Name</string>
    <string name="course_dialog_group_code">Group Code (Ex: EE241C7A)</string>
    <string name="course_dialog_extra">The guide can be found in the Setting tab. Please delete any unrelated course by check the course\'s faculty. This process is done automatically. Lowercase letters are acceptable.</string>

    <!-- timetable -->
    <string name="timetable_recheck">Recheck Timetable Online</string>
    <string name="timetable_list">Timetable List</string>
    <string name="timetable_save">Save as PNG</string>

    <!-- common -->
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="not_available">n/a</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>

    <!-- guide -->
    <string name="guide">
        This application is based on iCress website.
        Any information regarding your timetable or course registration is not hosted by Minima developer.
        You can add your course by press the \"Add course\" button on the top of the screen.
        You need to fill your \"Course code\" and \"Group name\" based on your course registration slip.
        Press \"Add\" button to find for the course specified online.
        It will automatically add if there is course available.
        Long press on a course to edit the course name or delete the course from your timetable.
        Press back to cancel the option.
        You can automatically recheck your timetable for changes on iCress by clicking \"Recheck Timetable Online\".
        This functionality is replaced by the \"Open Student Portal\" setting.
        It will open student portal using your Android phone\'s default browser.
        You can send feedback via email by clicking on the \"Feedback\" option.
        Press \"Minima vX.X.X\" setting to visit the company website.
        You can now save table as image by clicking \"Create Table\" setting and click on \"Save as PNG\" button.
        You can also reset all your timetable data, including courses by click on the \"Reset Timetable\".
        You can refresh your timetable by clicking the top right icon on the widget.
        You can also open your timetable directly from widget by clicking on the day display on the widget.
        This option only natively available for Android 7.1 and above or use any compatible launcher application available in the Play Store.
        You can long press the application icon to see the two shortcuts available: iCress and simsweb.
        These shortcuts can be dragged into your home screen.
        These shortcuts will open iCress or simsweb webpage from your default browser.
    </string>

</resources>
